then let me position myself that security is there
I took my last 70 reals from the account
no packaging
without logo
only I this cardboard box
let's get into gear
thank you brother
Charlie Brown Junior
edible skate wheel let's be pix
tamo together
Brown isn't worth it folks
brownie
edible skate wheel
tamo together
so it's not actually Brown in San Roger
of edible skateboarding
calling Charlie Brown Junior
today is 1 little more delicious
because the investigations have not yet arrived
I apologize
but it's all for you
how much does it cost
1st 10reals every 1
see how God acts silently in our lives
guy and we don't understand
sales are super weak
I'm here trying to sell my brownies and ride
my brand
i get a message from chorão brother inviting me
to go to his bar today
if you say that this is not God acting in our life
I don't know what it is
is on
caraca I ran out to get the bus
yes brownie bro
thank goodness I put 1 cute little plastic
turned on
looks like saturday is the best day
thank you brother
gratitude good hand
tamo together
stale hand
cool you are here
we are very nice
brownie
I say Charlie
you say
brownie
Charlie
it's us fucking
it is surreal to speak
I'm still saving some answers
but from the heart
I feel like I'm going the right way
I'm even voiceless
until tomorrow